Rose Gerlach Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Conde, Miguel (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Conlon, William, b. 1941 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Reese Palley gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Cooke, Robert (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Benedek gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Corbett, Edward, 1919-1971 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Corita (St. Corita students) 1965 (6 slides) (Box 2)
- Corkery (1slide) (Box 2)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1970 (Box 2)
- Corneille (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Levebre gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 2)
- Corwin, Sophie (9 slides) (Box 2)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Costa, Toni (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Waddell gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Cottingham, Thomas (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Courtright, Robert, b. 1926 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Feigen gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Cowels, Fleur (10 slides) (Box 2)
  - Hammer gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Cply, Bill (35 slides) (Box 2)
  - Iolas gallery, 1966, 1967, 1970, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Dwan gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Craig, Martin, b. 1941 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Crampton, Rollin McNeil, 1886-1970 (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Stable gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Crawford, Ralston, 1906-1978 (1slide) (Box 2)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Creo (22 slides) (Box 2)
  - ACA gallery, 1966, 1969, 1971 (Box 2)
- Crile, Susan, b. 1942 (12 slides) [Slide box 11] (Box 2)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 2)
- Crist (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - Smolin gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Cross, Carolyn (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Crotti, Jean (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1970 (Box 2)
- Crovello, William (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Sachs gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Cuixart (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Bonino gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- Cuna Indians (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Cunningham, Ben, 1904-1975 (12 slides) (Box 2)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 2)
- Cuppaidge, Virginia, 1943 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Sachs gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Dabo (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Graham gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Dado (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1965, 1966, 1970 (Box 2)
- Daphnis, Nassos, b. 1914 (21 slides) (Box 2)
  - Castelli gallery, 1964, 1965, 1968, 1971, 1973 (Box 2)
- Dallegret, François, b. 1937 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Waddell gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Dantzic, Cynthia Maris, b. 1933 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- D'Arcangelo (20 slides) (Box 2)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Dash, Robert Warren, b. 1934 (8 slides) (Box 2)
  - Graham gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Dashaloff, George (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - XX West gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Davie, Alan, b. 1920 (7 slides) (Box 2)
  - M. Jackson gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Davis, Gene, 1920-1985 (30 slides) (Box 2)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Jewish Museum, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1969, 1970, 1971, 1973 (Box 2)
- Davis, Ronald Wendell, b. 1937 (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Castelli gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Davis, Stuart, 1894-1964 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Rubin gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Day, John, 1932-1984 (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- De Amarol, Olga (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- DeAndrea, John, b. 1941 (8 slides) (Box 2)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- DeBlasi (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- De Castro, Amilcar, b. 1920 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Dechar, Peter, b. 1944 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1966, 1968 (Box 2)
- DeForest, Roy Dean, 1930-2007 (11 slides) [Slide box 12] (Box 2)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1966, 1972 (Box 2)
- DeFrance (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1970 (Box 2)
- deKanelba (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Cisneras gallery (Box 2)
- deLap, Tony, b. 1927 (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Elkon gallery, 1965, 1970, 1973 (Box 2)
- Deleveryas, L. (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Schoelkopf gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- DeMaria, Walter, b. 1935 (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - Dwan gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 2)
- Demuth, Charles, 1883-1935 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - "My Egypt," 1927, oil (Box 2)
- Del Pazzo (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Loeb-Krugier gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Delvaux, Paul, 1897-1994 (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Denes, Agnes C., b. 1938 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Dennis, Donna, b. 1942 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- DeNiro, Robert, 1922-1993 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Sachs gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- deRivera (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- DeRomans, Maria-Louisa (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Iolas gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Dessner, Murray (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- de Saint Phalle, Niki, 1930-2002 (35 slides) (Box 2)
  - Gimpel-Weitzenhoffer gallery (Box 2)
  - Iolas gallery, 1964, 1965, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Central Park Sculpture garden, 1968 (Box 2)
- de Se(u?)vero, Mark (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Green gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- de Vito, Ferdinand, b. 1926 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- Dewasne, Jean, 1921-1999 (9 slides) (Box 2)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Diamond, Dale (9 slides) (Box 2)
  - XX West gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Diamond, Martha, b. 1944 (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - "Under Heaven," 1983 (Box 2)
  - "Heavy Duty," 1983 (Box 2)
  - "Downtown," 1981 (Box 2)
- Diao, David, b. 1943 (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Castelli gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Reese gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Diaz-Balart (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Bonino gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- Dibbits, Jan (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Castelli gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Dickinson, Edwin Walter, 1891-1978 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Graham gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Dickstein (7 slides) (Box 2)
  - Stable gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Diebenkorn, Richard, 1922-1993 (7 slides) (Box 2)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Dienes, Ben (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - XX West gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Dienes, Sari, 1898-1992 (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - AIR gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Dill, Laddie John, b. 1943 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Diller, Burgoyne, 1906-1965 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - 1964 (Box 2)
- Dimeo, D. (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Dine, Jim, b. 1935 (15 slides) (Box 2)
  - Jackson gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Graham gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1970, 1971, 1973 (Box 2)
- Dix, Harry (29 slides) (Box 2)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965, 1968 (Box 2)
- Dobkin (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Forum gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Dogancay, Burhan Cahit, b. 1929 (10 slides) (Box 2)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 2)
- Dolnick, Judith (4 slides) [Slide box 13] (Box 3)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Domnitz (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Domoto (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Jackson gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Donati (27 slides) (Box 3)
  - Hammer gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1966, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 3)
- Dörflinger, Johannes, b. 1941 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
- Douaily, Saliba (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Dove, Arthur Garfield, 1880-1946 (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 3)
- Downey, Juan, b. 1940 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Wise gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
- Downing, Thomas, 1928-1985 (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Doyle, Thomas J., b. 1928 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Dwan gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Drachler, Jacob (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Drake, Teddy Millington, 1932-1994 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Byron gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Draper, William Franklin, b. 1912 (9 slides) (Box 3)
  - Graham gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 3)
- Drexler, Sherman, b. 1925 (11 slides) (Box 3)
  - Graham gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Drosd, Nancy (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Drummond, Sally (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Fischback gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Dubuffet, Jean, 1901-1985 (13 slides) (Box 3)
  - Pace gallery, 1968, 1971, 1972 (Box 3)
- Ducmann (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - XX West gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Duff, John (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Myers gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Dujouny (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Dunn, Anne, b. 1929 (9 slides) (Box 3)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1967, 1968, 1972 (Box 3)
- Duran, Robert (9 slides) (Box 3)
  - Bykert gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1971 (Box 3)
- Durchaex (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Graham gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Durkee (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Stone gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Dutary, Alberto, 1932-1998 (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Bodley gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Dworzan (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
- Dzubas, Friedel, 1915-1994 (30 slides) (Box 3)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1966, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Rubin gallery, 1971, 1972, 1973 (Box 3)
- Eakin (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Myers gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Ebbenson, Leonard (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Feigen-Herbert gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Eddy, John (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - French gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Edelheit, Martha (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Byron gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Ekstrom (3 slides) [Slide box 14] (Box 3)
  - Viviano gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- El Glaou, Hassan (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Hammer gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Elliot, Ronnie (8 slides) (Box 3)
  - Granville gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Eloul, Kosso, b. 1920 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Elta (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Midtown gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Emeric (19 slides) (Box 3)
  - Emile Walter gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 3)
- Emory, Lynn (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - 1964 (Box 3)
- Enders, Cleade (10 slides) (Box 3)
  - Bodley gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Engel (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Engel, Jules, 1909-2003 (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1966, 1968 (Box 3)
- Engman, Robert, b. 1927 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Myers gallery, 1972 (Box 3)
- Epko (12 slides) (Box 3)
  - Vercel gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Erdman, A. (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Ernst, Jimmy, 1920-1984 (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Ernst, Max, 1891-1976 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Jewish Museum, 1966 (Box 3)
- Erythropel (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Estes, Richard, b. 1932 (8 slides) (Box 3)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 3)
- Etrog, Sorel, b. 1933 (10 slides) (Box 3)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Everett, Bruce, b. 1942 (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972 (Box 3)
- Evett, Kenneth, 1913-2005 (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Krauschaar gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Faden, Larry (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Bowery gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Falkenstein, Clair, 1908-1997 (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Fanger, Walter (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - FDU gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Farber, Manny, b. 1917 (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 3)
- Farreras, Francisco, b. 1927 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Farris, Jos. (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Eggleston gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Faulkoner, Mary (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Fautrier, Jean, b. 1898-1964 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
- Fawcett, John (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Febland (27 slides) (Box 3)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Feigenbaum, Harriet, b. 1939 (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Feitelson, Lorser, 1898-1978 ( 5 slides) (Box 3)
  - White gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Feldstein, Mark, b. 1937 (11 slides) [Slide box 15] (Box 3)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Myers gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Ferber, Herbert, 1906-1991 (10 slides) (Box 3)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1967, 1969, 1972 (Box 3)
- Fernandez-Muro, Jose Antonio, b. 1920 (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - Bonino gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Ferrara (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Stone gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Ferrara, Jackie, b. 1929 (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Sachs gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Ferren, John, 1905-1970 (29 slides) (Box 3)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Sachs gallery, 1972 (Box 3)
- Ferreros (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Ferri, Renaldo (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - Iolas gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Ferro, John, b. 1942 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Stein gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Sachs gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Festival of Lights (11 slides) (Box 3)
  - Wise gallery, 1967, 1968 (Box 3)
- Filkosky, J. (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Filmus, Michael, b. 1943 (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - David Findlay, Jr. gallery (Box 3)
- Fine, Perle, b. 1908-1988 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Graham gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Finkelstein (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Fiore, Joseph (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Green Mt. Gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Firestein (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Phoenix gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Fish, Janet, b. 1938 (11 slides) (Box 3)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
  - R. Miller gallery, 1977, 1979, 1980 (Box 3)
- Flack, Audrey, b. 1931 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - French gallery, 1972 (Box 3)
- Flanagan, Barry, b. 1941 (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Flatsfixed Gallery (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - 1971 (Box 3)
- Flavet, Claude, b. 1940 (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - Wickersham gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Flavin, Dan, 1933-1996 (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - Dwan gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 3)
- Fleminger (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Auslander gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Floch, Joseph, 1895-1977 (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Forum gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Fogel, Jacqueline (14 slides) (Box 3)
  - Krasner gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 3)
- Fogel, Seymour, 1911-1984 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Folon, Jean Michel, 1934-2005 (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Fondacero (8 slides) (Box 3)
  - Ward Eggleston gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Fontana, Bill, b. 1947 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Iolas gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Ford (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Cordier-Eckstrom gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Forman, Alice (5 slides) [Slide box 16] (Box 3)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1979, 1980, 1983 (Box 3)
- Formicola, John Joseph, b. 1941 (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Forrester, Patricia Tobacco, b. 1940 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1983 (Box 3)
- Forsman, Chuck, b. 1944 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Francis, Sam (31 slides) (Box 3)
  - Matisse gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Jackson gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 3)
- Francis, Sherron (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Franconi (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Frankenthaler, Helen, b. 1928 (22 slides) (Box 3)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1966, 1968, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Rubin gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Whitney Museum, 1969 (Box 3)
- Frasconi, Antonio, b. 1919 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Fraser, Hamilton, b. 1966 (31 slides) (Box 3)
  - Paul Rosenberg gallery, 1966, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 3)
- Frazier (2 slide) (Box 3)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Freeman, John (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Freilich (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Roko gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Freilicher, Jane, b. 1924 (22 slides) (Box 3)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1967, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1968, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Myers gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Freund (21 slides) (Box 3)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Fried, Otto, b. 1922 (13 slides) (Box 3)
  - Byron gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Friedberg, Richard, b. 1943 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Friedeberg, Pedro, b. 1937 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Byron gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 3)
- Friedenthal (2 slides) [Slide box 17] (Box 3)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Fuki (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Fukui, Nobu (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Daniels gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972, 1973 (Box 3)
- Fuller, Sue, b. 1914 (15 slides) (Box 3)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 3)
- Fun on 57th St. (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Various Artists (Box 3)
  - Wise gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Furukawa (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Easthampton gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Gaitonde, Vasudev S., b. 1924 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Willard gallery, 1965, 1969 (Box 3)
- Galkin, G. (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Games (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Garcia Lopez, Antonio (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Garrett, Lillian (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Garston (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Greenross gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Gatch, Lee, 1902-1968 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1972 (Box 3)
- Gedeohn (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Stable gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Gelb, Jan, 1906-1978 (9 slides) (Box 3)
  - White gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Gelfmann-Pereira, Marylin, b. 1939 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972, 1974 (Box 3)
- Geiss, William (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- George, Herbert, b. 1940 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Stable gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
- Gentils, Victor A., 1919-1997 (13 slides) (Box 3)
  - Finch College, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Bonino gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Gentle, Esther (aka Esther Rattner) (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Bodley gallery, 1965, 1972 (Box 3)
- Gerardia, Helen, b. 1913 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Gesner, Herbert (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Feigen-Herbert gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Gianokos, Christos (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Sachs gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
  - 100 Acres gallery, 1972 (Box 3)
- Gibbs, David (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Feigen gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Gikow, Ruth, 1915-1982 (5 slides) (Box 3)
  - Forum gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Gilardi (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Gilbert and George, English sculptors, working together from 1967 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 3)
- Giles, William (23 slides) (Box 3)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1967, 1968 (Box 3)
- Giles (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Iolas gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Gilliam, Sam, b. 1933 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Byron gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Ginnevar, Chuck (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Giobbi, Edward Giochino, b. 1926 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Giordano, Joe (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Green Mt. gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Gladstone, Gerald, b. 1929 (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Graham gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Glassner, Lester (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
- Glyn, Cliff (16 slides) (Box 3)
  - XX West gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Glynn (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Golbin (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Grand Central Moderns gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Godard, Gabriel, b. 1933 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Findlay gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
- Goldberg, Rube, 1883-1970 (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - Hammer gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Goldblatt, Joel (9 slides) (Box 3)
  - Peridot gallery, 1964, 1966, 1971 (Box 3)
- Goldin, Leon, b. 1923 (4 slides) [Slide box 18] (Box 3)
  - Kraushaar gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Goldring (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1966 (Box 3)
- Goldstein, Julius (7slides) (Box 3)
  - Babcock gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 3)
- Goodman, Sidney, b. 1936 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Goodnough, Robert, b. 1917 (39 slides) (Box 3)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1972, 1973 (Box 3)
- Goodyear, John L., b. 1930 (13 slides) (Box 3)
  - Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Amel gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 3)
- Gorchov, Ron, b. 1930 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Gordon, Harvey (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1971 (Box 3)
- Gorski (9 slides) (Box 3)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Gottlieb, Adolph, 1903-1974 (2 slides) (Box 3)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1966 (Box 3)
- Gourevich, Jacqueline (11 slides) (Box 3)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1971, 1972, 1973 (Box 3)
- Gourfain, Peter (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Bykert gallery, 1968, 1972 (Box 3)
- Grafen, John (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Graham, J. (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1966 (Box 3)
- Graham, Robert (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 3)
- Grashow, James, b. 1942 (9 slides) (Box 3)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 3)
- Graves, Nancy, 1940-1995 (15 slides) (Box 3)
  - Graham gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Knoedler gallery, 1981, 1983 (Box 3)
- Gray, David (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Feigen gallery, 1965 (Box 3)
- Graziani, Sante, b. 1920 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Babcock gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Grebenak, Louis Arthur, 1913-1971 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Castelli gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Auslander gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Greenberg, Jake (1 slide) (Box 3)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 3)
- Greene, Stephen, 1918-1999 (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1969 (Box 3)
- Greenly, Colin (11 slides) (Box 3)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1964, 1965, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1968 (Box 3)
- Greenstein, Ilise (4 slides) (Box 3)
  - Sachs gallery, 1964 (Box 3)
- Griffa, Giorgio, b. 1936 (3 slides) (Box 3)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1970 (Box 3)
- Griefen, John, b. 1942 (7 slides) (Box 3)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1969, 1970, 1973 (Box 3)
- Grillo, Sarah (6 slides) (Box 3)
  - Byron gallery, 1967 (Box 3)
- Gross, Sidney (6 slides) [Slide box 19] (Box 4)
  - Rehn gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Grossman, Nancy (8 slides) (Box 4)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1980 (Box 4)
- Grooms, Red (23 slides) (Box 4)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966, 1967, 1969, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Myers gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Grosvenor (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Grover, Beatrice, active 1923-1947 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1965 (Box 4)
- Gruber, Aaronel deRoy, b. 1918 (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Gruner, A.D. (9 slides) (Box 4)
  - Jason gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Guerin, John (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - Kraushaar gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Guernsey, Kazuko (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Guerrero, Jose (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Graham, gallery, 1970 (Box 4)
- Guglielmi (1slide) (Box 4)
  - Nordness gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Gujrals (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Forum gallery, 1964 (Box 4)
- Gundelfinger, John, b. 1937 (13 slides) (Box 4)
  - Myers gallery, 1971, 1972, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1984 (Box 4)
- Gunderson, Karen (5 slides) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1983, 1984 (Box 4)
- Gunther (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Günther, Anna (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Gurevitch (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Roko gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Gursay, Ahmet (3 slides) (Box 4)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1968 (Box 4)
- Gussow, Alan, 1931-1997 (27 slides) (Box 4)
  - Peridot gallery, 1964, 1967, 1969 (Box 4)
- Gutierrez (6 slides) (Box 4)
  - 20th century West gallery, 1967 (Box 4)
- Guttuso, Renato, 1912-1987 (4 slides) (Box 4)
  - Forum gallery, 1969 (Box 4)
- Gwathmey, Robert, 1903-1988 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Haacke, Hans, b. 1936 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Wise gallery, 1966 (Box 4)
- Haas, Richard, b. 1936 (1 slide) (Box 4)
  - 100 Acres gallery, 1972 (Box 4)
- Haber, Ira Joel, 1947 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Hacklin, Allan (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Lo Guidice gallery, 1973 (Box 4)
- Haerer, Carol, b. 1933 (2 slides) (Box 4)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1971 (Box 4)
- Halkin, Theodore, b. 1924 (1 slide) (Box 4)